// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which country won the first ever World Cup in 1930?",
    answer: "Uruguay",
    options: [
      "England",
      "USA",
      "Uruguay",
      "Argentina"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which country has won the most World Cups?",
    answer: "Brazil",
    options: [
      "France",
      "Brazil",
      "Argentina",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals, but never won the competition?",
    answer: "Netherlands",
    options: [
      "Greece",
      "Italy",
      "Ukraine",
      "Netherlands"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which country hosted 2010 world cup?",
    answer: "South Africa",
    options: [
      "Ghana",
      "South Africa",
      "Mexico",
      "South Korea"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In which World Cup did Diego Maradona score his infamous 'Hand of God' goal?",
    answer: "Mexico 1986",
    options: [
      "Mexico 1986",
      "Italy 1968",
      "Germany 1986",
      "Argentina 1986"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "FC Barcelona",
      "Real Madrid",
      "Chelsea",
      "Liverpool"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who is the Champions League's top goalscorer of all time?",
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Diego Maradona",
      "Pelé"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which outfield player appeared in the Champions League final in three different decades?",
    answer: "Ryan Giggs",
    options: [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Ryan Giggs",
      "Ronaldinho Gaúcho",
      "Lionel Messi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which club is sometimes referred to as FC Hollywood?",
    answer: "Bayern Munich",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Manchester United",
      "Tottenham",
      "Bayern Munich"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which year was the first European Championship held?",
    answer: "1960",
    options: [
      "1960",
      "1961",
      "1962",
      "1963"
    ]
  },
];
